newarticle.eu 2012-05-03

# Privacy Policy & Liability Statement for NewArticle.eu

**How we gather information from users**

Our information collection depends on what page you are visiting, as well as what portions of this website you elect to provide the information. When you register for an author account, you will be asked to privde certain information. Additionally, you may be asked to provide information for access to certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase. Like most Web sites, NewArticle.eu  also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic  tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit, such as your login username. Among other things, the cookie may store your password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit.

In certain cases, you may choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site.

**What we do with the information we collect**

Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and do not share your information with anyone.

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you individually.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on www.NewArticle.eu to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by www.NewArticle.eu and other topics we think you might find of interest.

Personally Identifiable Information collected by NewArticle.eu may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions, administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service for example) may access such information. We will use your information only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

**Your Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacypolicies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, NewArticle.eu has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

**Our Commitment To Childrens Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, NewArticle.eu will never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.

Under our Terms of Service, children under 18 are not allowed to access our service.

**Collection of Personal Information**

When visiting NewArticle.eu, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links to third party Websites**

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**Children**

NewArticle.eu does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe NewArticle.eu has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us at the address listed below.

**Contacting Us**

We can be reached by emailing us to “ poston @ Newarticle.eu  “ , or contact us thru our contact form : [contact form](http://newarticle.eu/contact-us "Contact Us Page")

**Changes to this Policy**

NewArticle.eu reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

**Governing law**

This policy and the use of this Site are governed by Romanian law. If a dispute arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed-upon mediator in the following location: Romania. Any costs and fees other than attorney fees associated with the mediation will be shared equally by each of us.

If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through mediation, we agree to submit the dispute to binding arbitration at the following location: Romania, under the rules of the Romanina Justice. Judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitration may be entered in any court with jurisdiction to do so.

This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

**Content posted by other authors**

We do not take any responsibility of the content of posts made by other authors. The authors are fully respons

_Authors_  are  _fully responsible_  for statements made in their articles. Published articles do not necessarily reflect the views of NewArticle.eu.  NewArticle.eu does not assume any responsibility for the content of the authors posting

In preparation of this web site, every effort has been made to offer the most current, correct, and clearly expressed information possible. Nevertheless, inadvertent errors in information may occur. In particular, but without limiting anything here, the author of the NewArticle.eu  web site disclaims any responsibility for typographical errors and accuracy of the information that may be contained on the NewArticle.eu web pages. The information and data included on the NewArticle.eu web site have been gathered from a variety of sources, and are subject to change without notice to the Internet user. The author make no warranties or representations whatsoever regarding the quality, content, completeness, suitability, adequacy, sequence, accuracy, or timeliness of such information and data.

The author makes no representations or warranties regarding the condition or functionality or this web site, its suitability for use, or that this web service will be interrupted or error-free.

**Disclaimer or damages**

By using the NewArticle.eu web pages, the Internet user assumes all risks associated with the use of this site, including any risk to the Internet user’s computer, software or data being damaged by any virus, software, or any other file which might be transmitted or activated via the NewArticle.eu  web pages or the Internet user’s access to it. The author shall not in any event be liable for any direct, indirect, punitive, special, incidental, or consequential damages, including, without limitation, lost revenues, or lost profits, arising out of or in any way connected with the use or misuse of the information or lack of information on the NewArticle.eu web site or with the delay or inability to use this web site, or from any information, documents, services, software, or other material obtained through this web site, or otherwise arising out of the use of this web site, whether based on contract, tort, strict liability or otherwise. The author shall not be liable for any loss or injury caused in whole, or in part, by the actions, omissions, or contingencies beyond the author’s control, including in procuring, compiling, or delivering the information, or arising out of any errors, omissions, or inaccuracies in the information regardless of how caused, or arising out of any Internet user’s decision, or action taken or not taken in reliance upon information furnished.
